Abhishek Sharma

SUMMARY

Committed professional offering more than 1 years of experience in the field of web application development. Excellent communication skills and a consistent team player in all sorts of environments. Seeking to expand talents by bringing a wealth of expertise to a well-established company.

EXPERIENCE

Driver on hire - UI/UX Designer

Mumbai, India 03/2023 – 02/2024

- Made strategic design and user-experience decisions related to core functions and features.
- Built reusable code that could be utilised in other projects, saving company \$200.
- Proficient in JavaScript frameworks such as React Js, Next Js and Vue Js.
- Designed and implemented website interface for mobile, desktop and tablets.
- Built reusable code to utilise for other projects and to minimise costs.
- Contributed to back-end experience and collaborated on APIs.
- Worked with different testing tools and frameworks, content management systems and cross-functional teams to smoothly complete projects.
- Researched new programming languages, frameworks and technologies to stay abreast with latest trend.
- Laid groundwork of SEO to increase visibility and enable adding fresh pages to site.
- Liaised with team to develop content and choose applicable solutions to create and maintain website.

APACHI WEB TECHNOLOGY - HTML Developer

Mumbai, India 12/2022 - 02/2023

12/2022 - 02/2023

- Researched new programming languages, frameworks and technologies to stay abreast with latest trend.
- Responded to queries on private messages or comments to address issues and resolve complaints.
- Designed layout and graphics to enhance aesthetics and appearance of website.
- Created backup files on servers and directories to avoid data loss.

Mumbai, India 400097 7045630679 abhimp2477@gmail.com

SKILLS

- HTML, CSS, Bootstrap
- Javascript, Jquery, Material UI
- Figma, Photoshop, CorelDraw
- Website Optimisation, Debugging and Prototyping

EDUCATION

2020

J. M. Patel College of Commerce Mumbai, MH

BSCIT: 6.75 CGPA

2017

Sanskardham Jr. College

Mumbai, MH

HSC: 52.46%

2015

Swami Vivekanand High School

Mumbai, MH

SSC: 76.80%

CERTIFICATIONS

- 1st Prize National Science Olympiad (SSC -2015)
- 3rd Prize in Street Play (Mumbai University - UDAAN 2019)
- 1st Prize in Street Play (Mumbai University - UDAAN 2020)
- 2nd Prize in Inter-Collegiate Dance Competition